commercehq.com 2018-12-31

# CommerceHQ

**Commerce HQ Privacy Statement:**

CommerceHQ Inc **(“CommerceHQ”)** has created this privacy statement **("Statement")** in order to describe how we collect and use the personal information that (i) individuals provide on our website commercehq.com, and all its sub-sites and related sites (together, the **"Site"** ) and/or (ii) which is made available to us through our software as a service ecommerce platform **(“Service”)** that we provide to third party retailers **(“Retailers”)**. Our Service is described in more detail on our Site. 

Your privacy is of great importance to us. Please read the following to learn more about our Statement. By visiting or using the Website or Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Statement and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the ways set out in this Statement. 

**WHAT DOES THIS STATEMENT COVER?**

This Statement covers our treatment of personally identifiable information **(“Personal Information")** that we gather when you are accessing or using our Website or Services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Services (as that term is defined below). No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on the Services.

  1. **COLLECTED INFORMATION:**

    1. **Information collected from Retailers**

We collect your name, company name, address, email address, phone number(s) and credit card details. We collect data about the pages on our Website that you visit. We also collect data about how and when you access your account, including information about the device and browser you use, your network connection and your IP address. We collect Personal Information about your customers that you share with us or that customers provide while shopping or during checkout. We need this information to provide you with our Services; for example, to confirm your identity, contact you, and invoice you and so that you can process orders and better serve your customers.

    2. **Information collected from our Retailers’ customers**

We collect our Retailers’ customers’ name, email, shipping and billing address, payment details, company name, phone number, IP address and device data. We need this information to provide Retailers with our Services, including supporting and processing orders, authentication, and processing payments. We also use this information to improve our Services.

    3. **Information that is collected automatically**

CommerceHQ may also collect certain information from users of the Site and Service (including customers of our Retailers), such as Internet addresses, location and devices used and browser. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our Site in order to constantly improve the quality of the Service. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers and provide such information to third parties.

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, scripts and tags are used by us and our third party partners. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the website, tracking users’ movements around the site, and gathering demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing these types of tracking technologies.

Our third party partners also employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers' or Users' personal information.

Our website may include social media features, such as the Facebook Login or Like buttons, and widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

    4. **Cookies:**

When you interact with the CommerceHQ Website and Services we strive to make that experience easy and meaningful. When you come to our Web site or use our Service, our Web server sends a cookie to your computer. Cookies are files that Web browsers place on a computer's hard drive and are used to tell us whether customers and visitors have visited the Site previously. If you click on a link to a third party website, such third party may also transmit cookies to you.

Standing alone, cookies do not identify you personally. They merely recognize your browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to CommerceHQ, either by responding to a promotional offer, opening an account, or registering for a free trial, you remain anonymous to CommerceHQ. Cookies come in two flavors: session and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you've closed your browser or turned off your computer. They include such information as a unique identifier for your browser.

CommerceHQ uses session cookies containing encrypted information to allow the system to uniquely identify you while you are logged in. This information allows CommerceHQ to process your online transactions and requests. Session cookies help us make sure you are who you say you are after you've logged in and are required in order to use the CommerceHQ application. CommerceHQ uses persistent cookies that only CommerceHQ can read and use, to identify the fact that you are a CommerceHQ customer or prior CommerceHQ Website visitor (whatever the case may be). We are especially careful about the security and confidentiality of the information stored in persistent cookies. For example, we do not store account numbers or passwords in persistent cookies. Users who disable their Web browsers' ability to accept cookies will be able to browse our Website but will not be able to successfully use our Service.

  2. **USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

CommerceHQ uses the information that we collect to set up the Service for individuals and their organizations, to provide the Services and to continuously improve the Services. We may also use the information to contact customers to further discuss customer interest in our company, the Service that we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as promotions and events. Customers are invited to receive an email newsletter by providing an email address. Customer email addresses and any personal customer information will not be distributed or shared with any third parties.

Customers can opt out of being contacted by us, or receiving such information from us, at any time by sending an email to privacy@commercehq.com. Separately, customers are also asked to provide an email address when registering for the Service, in order to receive a username and password. We may also email information regarding updates to the Service or company, and will send a Customer Newsletter. Again, email will not be distributed or shared and customers can opt out of receiving any communication by emailing privacy@commercehq.com at the time it is distributed, or at the time any customer registers for the Service.

Where your use of the Services arises as part of your engagement with a business client of ours, we will share your interaction with that business which occurs through the Service with that business client. Except for this disclosure or except as we explicitly state at the time we request information, or as provided for below, in our terms of service or any other separate agreement which you may enter into with us, we do not disclose to any third-party the information provided.

  3. **THIRD-PARTY SITES:**

The Site and the Service may contains links to other web sites. CommerceHQ is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites. You will need to check the policy statement of these others web sites to understand their policies. If you access a linked site you may be disclosing your private information. It is your responsibility to keep such information private and confidential.

  4. **STORAGE LOCATION AND TRANSFER OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If you are located outside the United States, the information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored and processed at, a destination in the United States. By submitting information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Statement.

  5. **SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES**

    1. **Trusted Third Parties:**

We may from time to time employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide the Services to you. Unless we tell you differently, such third parties do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. This includes third party companies and individuals employed by us to facilitate our Services, including the provision of maintenance services, database management, Web analytics and general improvement of the Services, and businesses who engage our Services (to the extent provided for above).

    2. **Business Transfers:**

We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Also, if we (or substantially all of our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

    3. **Protection of CommerceHQ and Others:**

We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary to comply with law or a court order; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of CommerceHQ, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We also may be required to disclose an individual’s Personal Information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

    4. **With Your Consent:**

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

  6. **OPT-OUT POLICY:**

CommerceHQ offers its visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use information provided. If, at any time after registering for information or using the Service, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing your information with third parties or your consent on how we use your information, send us a request specifying your new choice. Simply send your request to privacy@commercehq.com

  7. **ACCESS - CORRECTING & UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION:**

If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at privacy@commercehq.com. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to CommerceHQ Inc. 8171 Yonge Street, Suite 365, Thornhill, ON, Canada, L3T 2C6.

  8. **CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT**

We may amend this Statement from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Statement in effect at the time such information is used. If we make material changes or changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email prior to the change becoming effective. You are bound by any changes to the Statement when you use the Website after such changes have been first posted.

  9. **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:**

Questions regarding this Statement or the practices of this Site should be directed to CommerceHQ's Security Administrator by e-mailing such questions to privacy@commercehq.com For more information, or if you have questions, please contact CommerceHQ by email at privacy@commercehq.com, or by post using the details provided below:

Commerce HQ Inc.   
Attn: Privacy Officer   
8171 Yonge Street, Suite 365, Thornhill, ON   
L3T 2C6   
Canada

© Copyright 2017 Commerce HQ, Inc. All rights reserved. Various trademarks held by their respective owners.

Effective Date: February 2017
